Guide to the David Tibet Current 93 archive, 1960s-circa 2013.
Tibet, David Current 93 archive
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
David Tibet Current 93 archive, 1960s-circa 2013.
8457
Tibet, David.
15 Cubic Feet.
Audio recordings, correspondence, photographs, publications, printed material, memorabilia.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The David Tibet Current 93 archive covers Tibet's life and career from his childhood to the present. The archive includes extensive manuscript material, a nearly-comprehensive collection of Tibet's musical releases and published books, production materials (including artwork proofs and album masters), unreleased writings and music recordings, and supporting ephemera. The archive represents a significant resource for the study of British underground/outsider music and art.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
David Tibet (né David Michael Bunting) is a musician, poet, visual artist, and publisher best known as the primary member of the music group Current 93. Tibet has been an influential underground figure since the early 1980s. Working initially in London's industrial music scene, Bunting--rechristened David Tibet due to his ownership of Tibetan musical instruments--performed with Psychic TV and 23 Skiddoo. In 1983, he began his own project, using the name Dogs Blood Order before settling on the Aleister Crowley-inspired name Current 93. The group's first single, "LAShTAL" (1983), was conceived by Tibet and John Balance as a one-off Crowleyan magical ritual on record. Soon after, Tibet began working with Steven Stapleton, who had been conducting surrealist musical experiments for several years under the name Nurse With Wound. Current 93's early work is heavily experimental, featuring distorted howling and tape loops. Perhaps owing to the growing list of collaborators (including Douglas P. of Death in June and Rose McDowall of the pop group Strawberry Switchblade), Tibet's music soon became more tonal and song-based, with a heavier emphasis on Tibet's poetic, mystical, and apocalyptic lyrics. Later musical collaborators such as Michael Cashmore, James Blackshaw, and Ben Chasny have led to even greater compositional intricacy in Current 93's music. Albums such as Thunder Perfect Mind, Of Ruine or Some Blazing Starre, and Black Ships Ate the Sky have been described as "apocalyptic folk," mixing Tibet's idiosyncratic lyrical outlook with music inspired by the British folk revival of the 1960s-70s. Other recordings in the collection include Perdition edition, Bite sized beasts, and Flawed existence.
In addition to his music, Tibet is a publisher, operating the Ghost Story Press from 1993-2004 to publish limited-edition reissues of Victorian ghost stories and supernatural literature. Durtro Press, founded in 1994, publishes reissues as well as work by more recent authors such as Thomas Ligotti, Baby Dee, and Tibet himself. Durtro was renamed Coptic Cat Press in 2008. Tibet is also active as a visual artist, with solo exhibits at the Isis Gallery (London) and White Columns (New York).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The David Tibet Current 93 archive covers Tibet's life and career from his childhood to the present. The archive includes extensive manuscript material, a nearly-comprehensive collection of Tibet's musical releases and published books, production materials (including artwork proofs and album masters), unreleased writings and music recordings, and supporting ephemera. The archive represents a significant resource for the study of British underground/outsider music and art.
Includes material by many of Tibet's collaborators and friends: John Balance (Coil), Genesis P-Orridge (Throbbing Gristle/Psychic TV), Peter Christopherson (Throbbing Gristle/Coil), Steven Stapleton (Nurse With Wound), Douglas P. (Death in June), Rose McDowall (Strawberry Switchblade/Sorrow), Tony Wakeford (Sol Invictus), Michael Cashmore (Nature & Organisation), Shirley Collins, Tiny Tim, Steve Ignorant (Crass), Annie Anxiety/Little Annie (Crass), William Breeze, Antony Hegarty (Antony & the Johnsons), Baby Dee, Ben Chasny (The Six Organs of Admittance), Thomas Ligotti, James Blackshaw, Nick Cave, Andria Degens (Pantaleimon), William Basinski, Christoph Heeman (H.N.A.S.), Chris Wallis, Matt Sweeney, Andrew WK, Maniac (Mayhem), Nick Salomon (Bevis Frond), Hilmar Örn Hilmarsson (HÖH), Einar Örn, Björk Guðmundsdóttir, William Bennett (Whitehouse), Diana Rogerson, and many others.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Tibet, David.; Antony.; Anxiety, Annie.; Baby Dee, 1953-; Balance, John.; Basinski, William.; Bennett, William (Double bassist); Björk.; Blackshaw, James, 1981-; Breeze, William.; Cashmore, Michael.; Cave, Nick, 1957-; Chasny, Ben.; Christopherson, Peter.; Collins, Shirley.; Degens, Andria.; Einar Örn Benediktsson, 1962-; Heeman, Christoph.; Hilmar Örn Hilmarrsson, 1958-; Ignorant, Steve, 1957-; Ligotti, Thomas.; Maniac.; McDowall, Rose.; P., Douglas, 1956-; P-Orridge, Genesis, 1950-; Rogerson, Diana.; Salomon, Nick.; Stapleton, Steven, 1957-; Sweeney, Matt.; Tibet, David; Tibet, David.; Tiny Tim.; W. K., Andrew (Wilkes-Krier); Wakeford, Tony, 1959-; Wallis, Christopher D.
Subjects:
Avant-garde (Music) -- Great Britain.; Music -- Great Britain -- 20th century.; Avant-garde (Music); Music
Places:
Great Britain
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Box 28 is closed to researchers.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Series II. Manuscripts and Documents
Series III. Production Materials and Artwork
Series IV. Photographs and Slides
Series V. Publications
Series VI. Audio/Visual Material
Subseries VI a. CDs (David Tibet Groups)
Subseries VI b. CDs (Other)
Subseries VI c. Records (David Tibet Groups)
Subseries VI d. Records (Other)
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1970, 1983-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2010-2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript correspondence (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Wedding correspondence, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
  - RESTRICTED material (Box 28)
- Series II. Manuscripts and Documents
  - Untitled manuscript and Coptic and Tibetan language class material (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "All the World Makes Great Blood" and other poems (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Manuscripts, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Xeroxed lyrics (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Duplicate/xeroxed lyrics (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - C93 old lyrics/promo sheet, invoices, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Current 93 text samples, manuscript (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Lumb's Sister" prints, manuscripts, C93 London Concert lay-out (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Geoff Cox's text for the CD/LP of The Inmost Light trilogy (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Gnostic Gnostril Codex 23, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Lyrics- Japan, University certificates (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Typed lyrics (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Lyrics, manuscripts, and notes (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Flat Earth Society certificate, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Short pieces by Tibet on Louis Wain (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Tibetan language exercise books, Undated (Box 25)
  - Coptic language exercise book (Box 25)
  - Notebooks, Undated (Box 25)
  - Notebook, 2009-2012 (Box 25)
  - Notebooks for learning Coptic, Greek, Akkadian, and Hieroglyphs, Undated (Box 25)
  - Datebooks, 2006-2011 (Box 25)
  - Notebook, 2000 (Box 25)
  - The Inmost Light journal, circa 1994-1995 (Box 25)
  - Journal, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Journals, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - The Ballad of Long Satan and Babylon, 1991 (Box 25)
  - Notebook, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Notebook, 1985-1987 (Box 25)
  - Journal, November 1992 (Box 25)
  - Tibetan notes (Box 25)
  - Tibetan notes, 1989 (Box 26)
  - Journal, Undated (Box 26)
  - Mixed content binder- lyrics, artwork, circa 1984-2003 (Box 26)
  - Two binders of lyrics and notes (Box 26)
  - Binder- Nanavesh 3 (Box 26)
  - Binder of Lyrics, 2009-2010 (Box 26)
  - Notebooks (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
  - Drafts of Ruine, Inmost Light, Soft Black Stars, and related unpublished material (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Lyric Printouts (Box 26, Folder 5-8)
  - Name tags and lanyards (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Ephemera cards and fliers (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Material from James Low's "Simply Being" (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Series III. Production Materials and Artwork
  - Material from publication of "Tatters and Whispers" (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ghost Story Press materials (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Flaxman Low, "Psychic Detective", 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Proofs for LP Lyric sheets for "Jhonn: Uttered Babylon" (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CD artwork (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Tamlin artwork (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Aleph endpapers and proofs, running sheets, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Proofs of the Durtro "Hand Printed by Alan anderson/ Tragara Pree" books by David Tibet, 2001, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Tales of the Supernatural" by James Platt, covers and proofs (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "The Collection of Strange Stories" by Robert Aickman, proofs (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
  - "Tales of the Grotesque" by LA Lewis, proofs, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - "They Might be Ghosts" by David Rowlands, proofs, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
  - "The Child of the Soul and Other Stories" by Stanislaus Eric, Count Stenbock, proofs, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "M.R. James Two Ghost Stories: A Centenary" proofs (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "The Story of a Troll-Hunt" by James McBryde, proofs, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Hypnagogue", 2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Corrected proofs and texts for the "Aleph at Hallucinatory Mountain" album (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - "Some Gnostic Cartoons" unbound, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "Invocation of Hallucinatory Mountain" spiral-bound, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "Near the Star of the Sun", David Tibet (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "The Haunted Head" by Nick Blinko (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rack cards, invitations, publicity (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Pussy Galore, Vagina Dentata Organ, and Supernatural Organization interviews (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Artwork, Current 93 stickers (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Heeman insert for LP not in collection (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NWW/unveiled LP jacket mock-up/prototype (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Proofs for "Who is the Sufferer?/What is the Suffered?" (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "Halo" photo and colour xeroxes of Loony Runes 12" Cover (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Babylonian drawings, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Artwork (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Master CD for the Mirror album on Durtro (Christopher Heeman) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Current 93 posters (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Current 93 posters (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Book and album artwork proofs (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - "Some Gnostic Cartoons" proofs (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Artwork portfolio (Box 27)
  - Artwork (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - Album artwork (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Series IV. Photographs and Slides
  - Wedding photographs, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 15-17)
  - Photo sets 0-21, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18-39)
  - Crystal Aura photos taken by Harry Oldfield (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photos in Moscow with David's friend, the Russian monk and priest Father Kosma, with others (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Death Mask cover by Steve (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Unlabelled photographs (Box 4, Folder 4-7)
  - Unlabelled negatives (Box 4, Folder 8-13)
  - Two black and white portraits (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Current 93 3D photos with glasses, April 14, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Unlabelled photographs (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled photographs and large slides (Box 7)
  - Wedding Photo Album (Box 8)
- Series V. Publications
  - "Sounds" newspaper, August 20, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Sounds" newspaper, October 1, December 3, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "The People" newspaper, July 24, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "Sounds" newspaper, February 9, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "Arthur" magazine, May, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous newspapers (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Articles, pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Blow Up. 97, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Wire, September 1997, January 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Ptolemaic Terrascope, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Record Collector, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - D-Side, May-June, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Terrorizer, January, November 2005; June 2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Zero Tolerance, May-June, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mojo, March, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Durtro Jnana Current 93 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Durtro Jnana Records (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Series VI. Audio/Visual Material
  - Subseries VI a. CDs (David Tibet Groups)
    - Johnsons with David Tibet, CD-2914 (Box 9, Box A)
      Joe's Pub April 2000
    - David Tibet and Steven Stapleton, CD-2915 (Box 9, Box A)
      Octopus
    - Steven Stapleton and David Tibet, CD-2916 (Box 9, Box A)
      The Sadness of Things
    - Current 93, CD-2917 (Box 9, Box A)
      A Little Menstrual Night Music
    - Current 93, CD-2918 (Box 9, Box A)
      Aleph at Hallucinatory Mountain
    - Current 93, CD-2924 (Box 9, Box A)
      Aleph at Hallucinatory Mountain (Russian
    - Current 93, CD-2919 (Box 9, Box A)
      All Dolled Up Like Christ
    - Current 93, CD-2920 (Box 9, Box A)
      All the Pretty Little Horses
    - Current 93, CD-2921 (Box 9, Box A)
      Aryan Aquarians: Meet their Waterloo
    - Current 93, CD-2922 (Box 9, Box A)
      As the World Disappears
    - Current 93, CD-2923 (Box 9, Box A)
      The Bells Shall Sound Forever
    - Current 93, CD-2925 (Box 9, Box A)
      Birdsong in the Empire
    - Current 93, CD-2926 (Box 9, Box A)
      Birdsong in the Empire (Russian)
    - Current 93, CD-2927 (Box 9, Box A)
      Black Ships Ate the Sky
    - Current 93, CD-2928 (Box 9, Box A)
      Black Ships Ate the Sky (Russian)
    - Current 93, CD-2929-2931 (Box 9, Box A)
      Black Ships At the Sky mix
    - Current 93, CD-2932 (Box 9, Box A)
      Black Ships Heat the Dancefloor
    - Current 93; Nurse With Wound, CD-2933 (Box 9, Box A)
      Bright Yellow Moon
    - Current 93, CD-2934 (Box 9, Box A)
      Calling for Vanished Faces
    - Current 93, CD-2935 (Box 9, Box A)
      Cats Drunk on Copper
    - Current 93, CD-2936 (Box 9, Box A)
      Christ and the Pale Queens Mighty in Sorrow
    - Current 93, CD-2937 (Box 9, Box A)
      The Courtyard/Jerusalem
    - Current 93, CD-2938 (Box 9, Box A)
      Crooked Crosses for the Nodding God
    - Current 93; Hoh, CD-2939 (Box 9, Box A)
      Crowleymass
    - Current 93, CD-2940 (Box 9, Box A)
      Current 93 at Bloomsburt Theatre
    - Current 93, CD-2941 (Box 9, Box A)
      Current 93 at Athens
    - Current 93, CD-2942 (Box 9, Box A)
      Current 93 at Glasgow
    - Current 93, CD-2943-2944 (Box 9, Box A)
      Current 93 at Rome
    - Current 93, CD-2945-2947 (Box 9, Box A)
      Dawn
    - Current 93; Death in June; Sol Invictus, CD-2948 (Box 9, Box A)
      Day of the Dawn
    - Current 93, CD-2949 (Box 9, Box A)
      Dogs Blood Order
    - Current 93, CD-2950-2951 (Box 9, Box A)
      Dogs Blood Rising
    - Current 93, CD-2952 (Box 9, Box A)
      Earth Covers Earth
    - Current 93, CD-2953-2955 (Box 9, Box A)
      Faust
    - Current 93, CD-2956 (Box 9, Box A)
      A Gothic Love Story
    - Current 93, CD-2957 (Box 9, Box A)
      A Great in the Small
    - Current 93, CD-2958 (Box 9, Box A)
      A Great in the Small (Russian)
    - Current 93, CD-2959-2960 (Box 9, Box A)
      Halo
    - Current 93, CD-2961 (Box 9, Box A)
      Harry Oldfield "Crystal"
    - Current 93, CD-2962 (Box 9, Box B)
      Hitler as Kalki
    - Current 93, CD-2963 (Box 9, Box B)
      Horsey
    - Xhol; Current 93, CD-2964-2965 (Box 9, Box B)
      Hot Buttered Xhol, with Xhol's Motherfuckers Live
    - Current 93, CD-2968 (Box 9, Box B)
      How I devoured Apocalypse Balloon (Russian)
    - Current 93, CD-2966 (Box 9, Box B)
      Hypnagogue
    - Current 93, CD-2967 (Box 9, Box B)
      Hypnagogue (Russian)
    - Current 93, CD-2969 (Box 9, Box B)
      I Have a Special Plan for this World
    - Current 93; Antony and the Johnsons, CD-2970 (Box 9, Box B)
      Immortal Bird/Cripple and the Starfish
    - Current 93, CD-2971-2972 (Box 9, Box B)
      Imperium
    - Current 93, CD-2973 (Box 9, Box B)
      Imperium (Russian)
    - Current 93, CD-2974 (Box 9, Box B)
      In a Foreign Town, In a Foreign Land
    - Current 93, CD-2975 (Box 9, Box B)
      Inerrant Rays of Fallible Sun (Blackship Shrinebuilder)
    - Current 93, CD-2976 (Box 9, Box B)
      The Inmost Light Third and Final
    - Current 93; Hoh, CD-2977 (Box 9, Box B)
      Island
    - Current 93, CD-2978 (Box 9, Box B)
      Judas as Black Moth
    - Current 93, CD-2979-2981 (Box 9, Box B)
      Live at Bar Maldoror
    - Current 93, CD-2982 (Box 9, Box B)
      The Menstrual Night
    - Current 93, CD-2983 (Box 9, Box B)
      Misery Farm
    - Current 93 and others, CD-2984 (Box 9, Box B)
      Myths 4
    - Current 93, CD-2985-2986 (Box 9, Box B)
      Nature Unveiled
    - Current 93 and others, CD-2987-2991 (Box 9, Box B)
      Not Alone
    - Current 93, CD-2992 (Box 9, Box B)
      Of Ruine or Some Blazing Starre
    - Current 93 and others, CD-2993 (Box 9, Box B)
      The Portable Altamont
    - Current 93, CD-2994 (Box 9, Box B)
      SixSixSix: SickSickSick
    - Current 93, CD-2995-2996 (Box 9, Box B)
      Sleep Has His House
    - Current 93, CD-2997 (Box 9, Box B)
      Sleep Has His House (Russian)
    - Current 93, CD-2998 (Box 9, Box B)
      Soft Black Stars (Russian)
    - Current 93, CD-2999 (Box 9, Box B)
      Soft Black Stars
    - Current 93 and others, CD-3002 (Box 9, Box B)
      Soundtrack to Infinity
    - Current 93, CD-3000-3001 (Box 9, Box B)
      The Spheres: One and Two
    - Current 93, CD-3003 (Box 9, Box B)
      Sveinbjorn Beinteinsson "Edda"
    - Current 93, CD-3004 (Box 9, Box B)
      Swastikas for Goddy
    - Current 93, CD-3005 (Box 9, Box B)
      Swastikas for Noddy
    - Current 93, CD-3006 (Box 9, Box B)
      Tamlin
    - Current 93, CD-3007 (Box 10, Box C)
      Tantric rNying.ma Chant of Tibet
    - Current 93 and others, CD-3008 (Box 10, Box C)
      Terra Serpentes
    - Current 93, CD-3009 (Box 10, Box C)
      Thunder Perfect Mind
    - Current 93, CD-3010 (Box 10, Box C)
      Thunder Perfect Mind (Russian)
    - Current 93 and others, CD-3011 (Box 10, Box C)
      Transmissions from Sinai
    - Current 93 and others, CD-3012 (Box 10, Box C)
      Untitled
    - Current 93, CD-3013-3014 (Box 10, Box C)
      When the May Rain Comes, with Sand's "Ultrasonic Seraphim"
    - Death in June, CD-3015 (Box 10, Box C)
      93 Dead Sunwheels
    - Death in June, CD-3016 (Box 10, Box C)
      Burial
    - Death in June, CD-3017 (Box 10, Box C)
      Paradise Rising
    - Durtro, CD-3018 (Box 10, Box C)
      World Serpent "Baby Dee"
    - Durtro, CD-3019 (Box 10, Box C)
      World Serpent
    - Durtro, CD-3020 (Box 10, Box C)
      Arthur Doyle, Edward Perraud, Dan Warburton "The Basement Tapes"
    - Durtro, CD-3021 (Box 10, Box C)
      Charlemagne Palestin "Karenina"
    - Durtro, CD-3022 (Box 10, Box C)
      Michael Cashmore "The Snow Abides"
    - Durtro, CD-3023 (Box 10, Box C)
      Michael Cashmore "Sleep England"
    - Durtro, CD-3024 (Box 10, Box C)
      The Apocalyptic Folk "The Nodding God Unveiled"
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3025 (Box 10, Box C)
      A Missing Sense
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3026 (Box 10, Box C)
      A Handjob from the Laughing Policeman
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3027 (Box 10, Box C)
      Alice the Goon
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3028 (Box 10, Box C)
      Alice the Goon LP Master
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3029-3030 (Box 10, Box C)
      An Awkward Pause
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3031 (Box 10, Box C)
      Angry Eelectric Finger
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3032-3033 (Box 10, Box C)
      Automating Vol I and II
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3034 (Box 10, Box C)
      Chance Meeting on a Defective Tape Recorder of a Sheep Ventilator and a Squeaky Metal Chair
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3038 (Box 10, Box C)
      Chance Meeting of a Defective Tape Machine and Migraine
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3035-3036 (Box 10, Box C)
      Chance Meeting on a Dissecting Table of a Sewing Machine and An Umbrella
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3037 (Box 10, Box C)
      Crumb Duck
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3039 (Box 10, Box C)
      Cadaverous Condition: Destroying the Night Sky
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3040 (Box 10, Box C)
      Drunk with the Old Man of the Mountains
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3041 (Box 10, Box C)
      Fifty Years of Sunshine
    - Nurse With Wound and others, CD-3042 (Box 10, Box C)
      Four Years in 30 Seconds
    - Nurse With Wound and others, CD-3043 (Box 10, Box C)
      Foxtrot
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3044 (Box 10, Box C)
      Funeral Music for Perez Prado
    - Nurse With Wound/John Contreras, CD-3045 (Box 10, Box C)
      Geometric Horsehair Cavalcade/Afraid 1 and 2
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3046 (Box 10, Box C)
      Gyllenskold/Brained
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3047 (Box 10, Box C)
      Homotopy to Marie
    - Nurse With Wound and others, CD-3048 (Box 10, Box C)
      Irreplaceable Hand
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3049 (Box 10, Box C)
      The Ladies Home Tickler
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3050 (Box 10, Box C)
      Large Ladies with Cake in the Oven
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3051 (Box 10, Box C)
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3052 (Box 10, Box C)
      Livin' Fear of James Last
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3053 (Box 10, Box D)
      The Little Dipper Minus Two
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3054 (Box 10, Box D)
      Lofoten Deadhead
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3055 (Box 10, Box D)
      Man With the Woman Face
    - Nurse With Wound and others, CD-3056 (Box 10, Box D)
      Masse Mensch
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3057 (Box 10, Box D)
      May the Fleas of a Thousand Camels Infest your Armpits
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3058 (Box 10, Box D)
      The Memory Surface
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3059 (Box 10, Box D)
      Merzbild Schwet
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3060 (Box 10, Box D)
      Minimal Track
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3061 (Box 10, Box D)
      The Musty Odour of Pierced Rectums
    - Nurse With Wound/irr.app.(ext.), CD-3062 (Box 10, Box D)
      Mute Bell Extinction Process
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3063 (Box 10, Box D)
      Od Lot
    - Nurse With Wound and others, CD-3064 (Box 10, Box D)
      Orang-utan
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3065 (Box 10, Box D)
      Rat Tapes One
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3066 (Box 10, Box D)
      Rock'n Roll Station
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3067 (Box 10, Box D)
      Salt
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3068 (Box 10, Box D)
      Salt: Marie Celeste
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3069 (Box 10, Box D)
      Second Pirate Session
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3070 (Box 10, Box D)
      Shipwreck Radio Volume One
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3071-3072 (Box 10, Box D)
      Soliloquy for Lilith
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3073 (Box 10, Box D)
      Soliloquy for Lilith extra tracks
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3074 (Box 10, Box D)
      Soresucker
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3075 (Box 10, Box D)
      Soundpooling
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3076-3077 (Box 10, Box D)
      Spiral Insana
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3078 (Box 10, Box D)
      Sugar Fish Drunk
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3079 (Box 10, Box D)
      Sylvie and Babshi-Fi Companion
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3080 (Box 10, Box D)
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3081 (Box 10, Box D)
      Purtle
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3082 (Box 10, Box D)
      To the Quiet Men from a Tiny Girl
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3083 (Box 10, Box D)
      Who Can I Turn to Stereo
    - Nurse With Wound and others, CD-3084 (Box 10, Box D)
      Wire Tapper
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3209 (Box 12)
      Stereo Wastelands
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3210 (Box 12)
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3216 (Box 12)